Loot, I am making this video so that
I can share proper information with all of you about
how much amount is required to buy a car, how much are the plane charges,
you will see that you can
subscribe as per your wish, any company
takes away the car forcefully,
subscribe, I recently bought a
car,
I had bought it a year ago also, then I was
forcibly taken ₹500 from him,
I did not do anything behind it,
simply I gave 500 and get the car repaired,
recently I had taken a claim, you
can see, I will show you, it is late,
I have bought it on 22nd 2022, you can
see all this, this is my online claim,
you will see, show it to him, see this, hence this is
598 of mine, you can also see
that the power meter, now the engine lagard one which was
written on the engine, take the pipe tailing
handle along with it, the side constipation is in the visor, there is
already a screen and
he forcibly added this to it,  It was of ₹10,
it was not attached, then I guided it, so the
total bill came to 259 and
you can see this here, look,
National Insurance Company Limited Kunnar in Delhi has invited
Hero Vertical Delhi, so that
I have taken this for my next, that is, I
need school EE, whatever is the demand, then
before the car was made, I said that a pass will be required,
I said okay, make it
like a car, they made it or they started
demanding your off date, so
as you will see, it will be written on the insurance that it will be
one hundred rupees, such compulsory access
pre-claim policy, so after that
what should I do, so I quickly got
a delivery from there, which is
National Insurance Company, I
drove it away from there
and
subscribed,
now you can see the number and this is the point
and the frustrated one of 248 was given directly to Hero,
after that they were demanding dowry,
now I have proof from both the sides and that
thing, this
subscription, if it happens automatically in
online system, then I took it
and it is on
both the sides  I
felt that for subscribing almost ₹500,
I had
subscribed here for ₹10, that
young man, because of which you can see that I
gave only ₹10 here, that he had taken 10 by
sitting forcefully, you can see this
and the packing of the train, this, this,
because of which I had to pay ₹10, not just ₹100
and this is available with him by doing the
positive way of his house and side
and almost total subscribe me
and
subscribe, you
get the delivery, take it,
I mean
how much did I get from my combine in this with insurance and I
mean and Gmail etc., then only the one with Hero
goes that there is no tension for Hero, you will get
Sita Vanvas on both sides, rest
see how it is with Aadhar company